You want to know what I think the problem is with people in the United States?
And I'm going to just keep it a bean.
I know people talk about Americans a lot, but I'm going to actually keep it a bean with y'all.
A lot of Americans believe that we give this.
We want to believe these are the people that we are.
When this is actually who we are.
This right here.
This is who we are.
We believe beyond a shadow of a doubt these are the people that we are.
We are this.
We think we are this.
When in reality, we are this.
This is what we are.
This.
We think this is us.
And I have bad news.
This is not us.
This.
This is us.
This is who we are.
Not the other one.
This.
We think we will be supporting this one.
No, we wouldn't.
We will be supporting this one.
As a country, this is who we will be getting behind.
This.
This is us.
This is who we'd be.
This is who we.
This is how we would show up in the film.
That is history.
Just in case y'all were confused.
I really hope this helps.
Clarify.
Okay.